Nan'an 1-Day Tour (Old Street & Ancient House Food, for tourists with tight schedules)
Why is it so noisy downstairs?
We've gone viral!
It's not us.
It's Tang Yi.
Today at the shop,
several customers came asking him for makeup and styling.
It's the video we went out to shoot the other day.
After you fell asleep,
I edited it and posted it online for promotion.
So did we go viral or did Mr. Tang?
Hurry up, wash up and let's go.
Stop talking about Mr. Tang all day.
What about Mr. Tang?
It's you.
Always talking about Mr. Tang.
Where are we going?
Did you just hear this part,
sister?
Although we didn't go viral,
at least we gained something.
Three orders.
Today,
we've already received deposits for three orders.
Thank you, Mr. Zhang.
Hurry up, pack up and let's go.
Stop dawdling.
What did you just call me?
Profiteer.
What do you mean?
Why is the first client so difficult?
Wait a minute.
No, aren't these just mochi?
The sizes are different,
and they are more expensive than downstairs.
It's like this,
Mr. Zhao.
These Yingdu mochi
use the best ingredients.
Yes.
And it's completely handmade.
Yes, that's right.
It's also a local intangible cultural heritage snack here.
So this...
You don't need to tell me all this useless stuff.
I don't buy it.
What's wrong? Do you think I'm too demanding?
No, Mr. Zhao.
Our company's lifelong goal
is that the customer is god.
Learn from this little brother.
Go ahead with your work.
Starting work
next Monday is fine.
But I have a quick question.
Is it possible
to increase
the housing allowance?
No problem at all.
What do you mean?
They are not the same thing.
What does he want?
Might as well press it out with a machine.
He's nitpicking.
No,
I'm not
complaining.
I...
No,
why are you telling me not to go?
Did you say it was handmade? Hands?
Who cares.
They are guests.
Can you tell?
They are of different sizes.
Look at the flour.
It's unevenly coated.
Full of flaws.
Sir, we just said it was handmade.
By hands.
How could I not know?
What she means is,
this mochi,
because it's handmade,
the sizes will vary.
But it tastes the same.
Please try it first.
No.
The soybean powder
isn't evenly coated on both sides.
And look at this shape.
It should be oval.
It tastes better this way.
Yes, Mr. Zhao.
If you really don't like it, just eat less.
Let's go to the next stop.
Watch your attitude.
Mr. Zhao, we're leaving first.
Let's go.
Why the long face?
Weren't you happy to pick up the client this morning?
It's not strange to see this expression on my sister's face.
If Zhang Yang did it,
it wouldn't be easy.
Have a pear.
My sister doesn't like pears.
Then what do you like to eat?
She likes to eat
oranges without pith.
Xinyue,
you guys really had a rough day today.
I took a client to eat braised noodles,
added some red mushrooms,
which turned the soup pink.
He insisted I brought him noodles with food coloring
and wanted to complain.
I said oyster omelets taste better with crispy edges.
He insisted I ruined it and was just making excuses,
and wanted to complain about me.
I took him to eat Popiah.
There were some chives inside.
He didn't say he doesn't eat them!
He insisted on blaming me,
and wanted to complain about me.
He said the name 'Pigu Noodles' isn't elegant,
and wanted to file a complaint about it.
He is not here for a tour at all.
He is just here to nitpick.
You saw it yourself today.
Along the way,
he made 8 or 9 phone calls.
He has a PhD.
He still hasn't found a job,
so it's understandable that he is anxious.
That's because he's so picky,
that he lost all opportunities.
I'm a tour guide.
I'm not his punching bag.
Look on the bright side.
It's only for three days.
Three days will pass quickly.
Just bear with it.
It's bad for your health to hold it in.
How about taking the client to
the Zheng Chenggong Memorial Hall?
It has a good meaning,
and we can encourage him along the way.
Not bad. You can only win if you fight for it.
Bad-tempered sister.
Cool down.
Idiot.
I'm so angry.
It's so sour.
Zheng Chenggong Memorial Hall.
Yes, sir.
Zheng Chenggong, a native of Nan'an,
is a national hero who expelled the Dutch colonists
and recovered Taiwan.
He is also an important part of Nan'an's history.
Are you reading from a script?
With your professional skills...
Be a bit more expressive.
You are absolutely right, sir. I'm sorry.
I will definitely give you an expressive explanation later.
All right. Let's go.
Okay.
Let's go.
Come, follow this way.
Hurry up and hold the flag up.
Mind the steps.
Everyone knows Zheng Chenggong's feat of recovering Taiwan.
But few people know
that before that,
he also suffered a tragic defeat.
Then tell me,
how did this hero fail?
Heroes are human too.
Life has its peaks,
and it has its valleys, right?
After that defeat,
his trusted aides advised him to retreat overseas temporarily
to plan for the future.
The tables will turn.
Don't bully the young and poor.
But he didn't agree.
He chose to return to his hometown immediately
to regroup.
He was 35 that year.
He was no longer a youth.
Men remain boys until death.
So, that led to his later heroic act
from 1661 to 1662,
where he spent ten months
expelling the Dutch colonizers
and recovering Taiwan.
Great.
Come to Nan'an, and you will succeed.
You only win if you fight.
You always say you only win if you fight hard.
So only those who win are heroes?
What about those who don't?
What are they?
What am I then?
A client.
Is this the time to be smart?
Let me tell you.
If it weren't for the free spot you gave me,
I wouldn't even have come.
Do you know why I'm unhappy?
Too utilitarian.
There are so many hurdles in life.
You're only successful if you overcome them.
If you can't, it means you didn't work hard enough.
So one fall ruins your whole life, right?
I really don't know
what you two are lecturing me about.
From yesterday till now,
everything you two
arranged for me
has failed to satisfy your client.
You've already fallen.
If one fall in life is the end,
Then life would be ruined long ago.
Is that how you talk to a client?
I didn't mean to insult him.
I was just stating a fact.
Look, everyone has to learn to walk when they are young.
And you're bound to fall when learning.
He said,
life is ruined once you stumble.
Then there are few whose lives wouldn't be ruined.
He's so picky about everything.
It's really annoying.
Okay, you're always right.
But he's the client.
He has the right to be picky.
Look, once the tour ends tomorrow afternoon,
if he files a complaint and reports you,
what will you do?
What will you do?
Why don't you apologize first?
Is there any other way besides apologizing?
I did.
Ask him. I apologized three times,
but he didn't accept it.
If my sister were here,
she would definitely scold him worse than I did.
Why are you bringing up your sister all of a sudden?
What's wrong with that?
She's my sister.
Okay.
You are all my sisters, all right?
Since when do you have so many sisters?
She's my sister.
You're baffling.